[music]
Hello and welcome to yet another
episode. Today we have a general topic
that everyone seems to be very concerned
about which is I mean can you blame
them? It's government corruption. We've
been living with it for years and today
we're going to attempt and kind of break
it down for people. What are the issues
that we need to address right away? What
are the issues that can be addressed
maybe a little bit later? We will bring
in current issues in Trump
administration and we will attempt to
break it down for you. So let's start
back.
>> And you know what's funny about that too
is that so many Americans don't really
think of the government as being
corrupt.
I remember serving in the in the State
Department overseas, right?
>> And complaining about corruption in the
Middle East because if you wanted to
have
>> your telephone line installed, these
were this I'm talking about the days
before cell phones, you had to slip the
guy a couple of hundred. Yeah. I had a
plumbing problem and I had to bribe a
plumber to come over to the house.
That's kind of petty day-to-day
corruption. The corruption that we're
talking about is is corruption like for
example
spending 30 years at the CIA, retiring
on a Friday, going back in on Monday
with a different colored badge, making
10 times what you were making at the
agency because you just joined your
buddy's LLC and you get a no bid
contract.
>> Absolutely.
>> That happens every single day. Crazy.
>> How is that not corruption? It's
American taxpayers money going to a
private company,
>> right?
>> To do exactly what the CIA was doing for
a tenth of the price. You and I offline
talked about a a company. I I won't name
it.
>> Yeah.
>> Just so that I can speak freely.
>> Right.
>> This company didn't exist in the very
early 1990s.
>> And then a very senior CIA officer
retired and just made an LLC. and he
only made it so he and his friends could
use it as a tax pass through and they
could smoke cigars and play cards and
hang out together and write it off as a
as a tax loss. Well, then their old
buddies from inside the CIA started
giving them no bid contracts. One thing
led to the other and by the end of the
decade, this was a multi-billion dollar
company. Multibillion dollar company.
And what's happened is that they were
passed no bid contracts and then as soon
as the person who authorized the
contract retired, the company would hire
that person and then the next generation
of senior CI officers would give them no
bid contracts. That's corruption. And
that happens every single day.
>> Absolutely. And you should know, like I
said, you worked for the agency, you saw
it. How unfortunate that you are not
part of it right now. Could you imagine
how much money you could have made?
rich. I'd be rich. And another another
thing that's kind of funny, not haha
funny, but in an ironic way,
>> is that
>> the government, not just the CIA, but
the CIA, the Pentagon, the State
Department, it's the whole national
security apparatus will make a very big
deal about
somebody wanting to win a Pentagon
contract or a CIA contract and taking
people out to a strip club, let's say,
right, to try to win the contract.
Oh, and then lo and behold, there's, you
know, a dozen felony charges pressed
against the person and then there's an
all hands email that goes out saying,
"Oh, don't do things like this. This is
corruption."
>> Right.
>> Well, it's a different kind of
corruption. Sure. But how have these
other guys gone through their whole
lives making between, you know, $50,000
and $180,000 and then they retire and
they're worth $25 million
>> all of a sudden. Absolutely. Because
they were uh little good boys when they
were in the, you know, agency and they
were kind of dosile horses and they got
what they got, you know, price unlike
you who actually blew the whistle and
[laughter] did the right thing. Did the
right thing. No, you go to jail. So, um,
let's talk about, you know, for some
people who still don't get it. Like when
we talk about military-industrial
complex and we speak about how corrupt
it is, people really, you know, you have
to understand they have their little
jobs or very important jobs or whatever.
There are many people out there who
don't pay attention to what's going on
in the government. Um, especially with
the military-industrial complex. So,
when we say it's corrupt, they don't
quite understand how. Let's talk about
rigging the prices. Let's talk about
revolving door. Let's let's talk about
how [snorts] government contractors are
getting way more for building the same
jet for example that uh you and I could
built like much cheaper. So could you
like explain to people where the price
rigging started?
>> This this is a problem that runs so
deeply, right,
>> that we won't be able to expose all of
it here on this show, but price rigging
has been a problem for the last 250
years. And it happens all the time and
sometimes people get caught and
sometimes they don't get caught. But
price rigging is a very big problem.
Right? Another problem is kickbacks,
>> right? So there was an admiral who was
just arrested, I'm going to say two
weeks ago uh for accepting kickbacks,
for approving a contract uh on a no, it
was a no bid contract. So that he got
his 10% or 5% or whatever it was. And
his only regret in his statement of
regret was that he got caught.
>> Wow.
>> This this kind of thing happens all the
time. So
>> let's talk about the F-35 as the most
obvious example.
>> Flying duck. That's what it is.
>> Everybody who knows anything about
military aviation said this F-35 was a
bad idea.
what the situation had been before the
development of the F-35 was that each
one of the uniformed services had its
own um fighter jets, right? F-14s,
F-16s, F-18s, everybody had their own
the A10 uh Warthog, everybody loved it.
Close in, you know, you could strafe
tanks or whatever. And then somebody had
the brilliant idea to make just one jet
that does everything.
Well, experts said, "Yeah, great idea.
Not possible.
>> Can't do it." Nonsense. Congress is
smarter than the experts. So, Congress
allocates billions upon billions of
dollars to develop the F-35 and they
give it to Loheed Martin. So, Loheed
develops it, gives it to all of the
uniform services. They try it out.
They're crashing. People are ejecting.
Uh, and then you can't sell it like
that,
>> of course.
>> So, you have to sell a degraded version.
>> I don't know if you if you know this. I
think most people probably don't know
it. You know it, but
>> for example, as it was being developed,
>> um, the Israelis came to us
>> and they said, "We want this F-35." And
we said, "Okay, you can be the first
country that gets the the F-35, but
we're going to slightly degrade the
avionics
because if one gets shot down, we don't
want the Russians or the Chinese or the
Iranians or anybody else to be able to
reverse engineer it to see what the F-35
can actually do. So, we're going to give
you the F-35, but we're going to call it
the F-35I
for Israel."
Okay? And then the Emirates said, "Well,
wait a minute. if you're going to give
it to the Israelis, we want the F-35,
too, because we live right next door to
the Iranians and we may need to fight
them. We said, "Okay, we're going to
give you the F-35E
for Emirates." So, it's the same as the
Israeli one, just with a different
letter. And we kept the F-35, the actual
F-35. That's great. But the problem is
none of them work as well as the F-14,16
and 18 were working or the A10 that
literally everybody loved that they
said, "Oh, well now that's from the
Vietnam War. We're going to stop making
it." Why? When it works and everybody
loves it. I was about to say like, you
know, if I was Israel,
>> hopefully never, but if I was, you know,
part of Israeli, you know, diplomatic
aspect of things or I wouldn't even buy
it.
>> Honestly, if if I was Israel or Saudi
Arabia, I wouldn't even buy a flying
Turkey.
>> Well, let me let me interrupt you. Yeah,
sure. That's true. But you know what
they did? You know what they did? They
took the F-35i
>> and then they they dispatched dozens of
spies all across the United States to
steal the information that would allow
them to upgrade the avionics to what the
US is using.
>> Wow.
>> Wow. Good luck with that. I mean, as I
understand, even with the avionics that
we are using, it's not
>> still no good.
>> Still no good.
>> This is this is part of an ongoing
problem. First of all, just to to tie
the knot on on the F-35, um
>> the Iranians claim that they've shot two
of them down
>> uh in in the last couple of days in this
in this war that they're having with uh
with the Israelis. The Israelis said
publicly, all F-35s return home. All
pilots are accounted for. But the
Iranians released a video of an F-35
being shot down north of Tehran and the
pilot parachuting down to safety.
>> Is this one of those Israeli ones that
we gave? You tell me.
>> Probably Beverly. Yeah, I would think
that's exactly what's happening. So,
yeah, but I as I understand we have F-22
that's equally expensive.
>> Uh not as expensive as F-35.
>> Nothing is as expensive as F35. F-35 was
supposed to be this like mega jet or
whatever. It didn't work out for them.
And I've spoken to pilots. That's why I
can simply say that's what they called
it, flying duck. Why? Because it's not
agile at all.
>> No. [laughter]
>> So, it's supposed to do everything. It's
supposed to be stealth
>> and then you can take off from a from an
aircraft carrier or from a land uh
runway and right
>> like why?
>> But as I understand, we're not selling
F-22. I could be wrong. um the rapture
because that that is more efficient
playing as I understand it.
>> That's my understanding as well.
>> Yeah. So, but do you think that any of
them are worth the money they that
American people are giving?
>> No. And this is another problem related
to corruption. The problem is year after
year after year going back to the 1950s,
the Pentagon will come in and say, "We
want X amount of money for next year's
budget." And Congress says, "We'll give
you that amount and we'll give you
another 15%." And the Pentagon says,
"That's great. We don't know what we'll
spend it on because [laughter]
we don't need it, but we'll take it.
>> Is it any wonder that the Pentagon has
failed seven consecutive audits to the
point where the [snorts] most important
auditing firm in the world, Price
Waterhouse Coopers, gave up in the
middle of the last audit and said it
can't be done. that fully half of the
Pentagon's hardware can't be located,
can't be accounted for.
>> Unbelievable.
>> If that's not the definition of
corruption, I don't know what is.
>> Yeah. And I have a question. Where is
this money? Where do you think is the
money? Where do you think it is?
>> I think most of it is probably just been
squandered. It's probably been wasted.
It's It's actually hard to steal
>> cash from government. There's always a
paper trail. It's very easy to get
caught,
>> right?
>> But it's very difficult to catch people.
Um,
>> could it be going to intelligence? Sorry
to interrupt. Could it be going to
operations overthrowing people and%
right?
>> 100% yes.
>> A lot of money.
>> There was a senator there was a
Democratic senator from Wisconsin named
William Proxm.
William Proxm was very very unusual for
a couple of reasons. First, he's the one
who took uh uh Joseph McCarthy's seat uh
when McCarthy died of alcoholism in the
1950s. You remember the McCarthy era and
the Red Scare?
>> So, Proxm was a liberal Democrat,
solidly liberal Democrat.
>> And if there was one thing that Proxm
hated, it was waste. Government waste.
So, in the 1970s, mid 1970s, he created
this kind of phony um award that he
would give out every month called the
Golden Fleece Award.
>> And it was a spray painted um sheep's
wool, spray painted gold, and it was he
would give it every month to the the
government agency or department that had
ripped off the American people, the
worst that month. Now,
>> that was a great idea, right? But it
used to drive the CIA absolutely crazy
because the CIA budget is secret or in
some cases top secret and it's never
published ever in American history. It's
never been published. What the CIA does
is it takes elements of the budget, line
items of the budget, and it sticks it in
everybody else's budget all around
government. So when you see a line item
in the Pentagon budget for $100 million
to study the mating habits of
Costa Rican snails. Okay. There is no
such program. That's just made up.
That's a CIA covert activity.
>> Is that real?
>> Yeah. Such things are real.
>> Yeah.
>> Or to help monkeys procreate or
something like
>> Yeah. Exactly. [laughter]
Those programs don't actually exist.
That money is secretly transferred to
the CIA so that it has its budget.
>> Well, then something like 9/11 happens
>> where the CIA gets a multi-billion
dollar supplement to its multi-billion
dollar budget
>> and it makes it that much more difficult
to hide it. Well, if you're if it's
secret in the first place and nobody
knows about it,
>> how hard could it be to steal from it?
>> Exactly. you know, even on a very small
scale. When I was in Pakistan, I was the
uh I was the head of CIA
counterterrorism operations in Pakistan,
and my budget there was literally
unlimited
>> and I spent millions of dollars. But I I
took this young first tour case officer
under my wing and I told her, "You're
going to have the most important job in
the station right now. You're going to
be the head of finance." Right? So every
dollar that we spend, every dollar that
we give to the Pakistanis, we have to
account for it. And when the operation
in this case to catch Abu Zuba um is
completed, we have to balance our books
to the dollar. I said, I'll tell you
something that my first station chief
told me there are only three people that
can wreck your career.
>> Security,
medical, and finance.
Finance can send you to prison.
She said, ' Okay. So, as part of these
operations, we bought more equipment
than you can shake a stick at.
Everything from battering rams to
bulletproof vests to night vision
goggles, guns, ammunition,
uh secure communications, encrypted
walkie-talkies, satellite dishes,
>> and at the end of it, headquarters said,
"Just throw it away or just give it to
the Pakistanis. We don't want to bring
it back.
>> Wow.
>> So I said to the brigadier general that
I was working with, Pakistani brigadier
general, "General Muhammad, we would
like to we would like to make a gift of
all this equipment." He's like, "Oh my
gosh, thank you so much. It's so
advanced. My people don't have any of
it." So it was truckloads of equipment.
>> Crazy. You mean like we we left bunch of
equipment in Afghanistan without
>> any Well, it's better. It's better than
that. It's better than that.
truckloads we delivered to him. And then
a couple of weeks later, I said to the
colonel, who was my day-to-day contact,
so glad you guys are going to be so well
equipped with with uh all the stuff that
we turned over. He said, "What stuff?" I
said, "Literally all the stuff, the
guns, the ammo, the battering rams, the
walkie-talkies, the satellites."
He said, "I don't know what you're
talking about. The general just took
it." And I can tell you what he did with
it.
>> Wow. He probably sold it
>> to the Taliban,
>> right?
>> Of course.
>> That is absolutely
crazy.
>> Sure. Because he wants to retire in a
nice big house someday, too.
>> So, [snorts] not only sometimes we
directly arm Taliban, sometimes we
indirectly [laughter] arm Taliban and
then we fight them. How smart. I mean,
it's unbelievable. And that that goes to
show how corrupt the government is. And
I remember you told me this. We can cut
it if you don't want it. Like simple
parking ticket. They used to tell you
not to spend less on a parking or
something like go and park in the most
expensive parking spot or was it like
something like that?
>> I'll I'll I'll tell you two short
stories related to that.
>> Yes.
>> Um
I would always fly out of Dulles airport
because that's the international airport
in Washington. So you can fly directly
to the Middle East and then from Dubai
or Doha you can go anywhere else that
you want. And sometimes you have to go
and switch out passports and what have
you depending on the operation that
you're doing. So I would always go and
when I had to park for more than, you
know, a couple of days, I would park in
the in the value lot, like the one where
you have to sit there for 45 minutes and
wait for the purple bus to come take
take you to the purple lot, right? So, I
was always very good about doing my
paperwork. And my boss came up to me one
day and he said, "Did you park in the
economy lot at the airport?" I said,
'Yeah. He said, "Why?" I said, "Cuz it's
$9 a day and the daily lot is $25 a
day." And he says, "Don't try to save
the government money."
>> [laughter]
>> Well, he told me later he parked in the
valet lot, which was $60 a day, and I'm
out in the $9 a day econ economy lot.
So, I continued to park in the economy
lot. It just didn't make sense to me to
just throw away
>> the American people's money. Well, one
day, a scientist from another country
arrived in Pittsburgh to uh attend a
seminar, and my boss said, "Hey, listen.
Ahmed Schmakmed is in Pittsburgh. I want
you to go bump him. Bump him means
approach him and say, "Hey, I know who
you are. You probably know who I am. You
know, we need to have dinner and a
conversation."
Well, I [snorts] don't remember why this
happened, but I had to change my pants
that morning [laughter] and I had my
driver's license
out
with a $5 bill, but my wallet with my
credit cards I left in my other pants.
So, I I'm busy. I'm nervous. I'm
thinking about how I'm going to do this
approach. and I go to the airport and I
don't have my wallet. I have my [snorts]
driver's license so I can get on the
plane and I have a $5 bill. That's it. I
said, "Oh my god, what am I going to do?
I'm going to get fired." So I get on the
plane, I fly to Pittsburgh.
Well, it's it's a $30 cab ride into town
and I only have $5 with no credit card.
So, I walk up to the Red Cross like
emergency aid desk and I said,
"Is there a is there a bus that goes
into Pittsburgh?" And she said, "Yeah,
it's long." She says, "It goes like to
every suburb before it gets to
Pittsburgh." I said, "How much is it?"
She says, "$250." I said, "Oh my god."
Okay.
So, I cash in my $5 bill for four ones
and four quarters. I go out to the bus
stop, get on the bus. It takes me like
an hour to go the seven miles, you know,
into Pittsburgh. I go, I bump the guy,
he tells me, "Go screw myself so there's
not going to be a dinner." I take the
bus back to the airport like this, get
on the plane, and fly to Washington. The
next day, I'm in the office. I fill out
my accounting paperwork. He comes up to
me and he says, "Damn you. Did you spend
$5 on that trip to Pittsburgh?"
[laughter]
And I said, "Yes, but listen, there's a
story behind it." And I told him, "I
just forgot my wallet." And I happen to
have a $5 bill.
Don't try to save the government money.
[laughter]
So the next trip was to Dubai and I was
just overnighting there because I had to
go on to, you know, one of the [__] hole
countries as Donald Trump said.
[laughter]
So I overnight and there happens to be a
Lebanese uh nightclub in the lobby of
the hotel. Very nice hotel.
>> So I went into the nightclub and I was
like the first person there because it
was like, you know, 7 o'clock,
>> right?
>> And they don't really get going till
like midnight. So I said, "Um, I don't
want to stay for the show. I just have a
real hankering for Lebanese food." And
he said, "Oh, well, we only sell the
package. It's the show and a big shisha
pipe." And I said, "I don't need any of
that stuff. I just want Lebanese food."
He said, "I have to charge you the full
thing." I said, "How much is it?" He
said, "$195."
I said, "Give it to me." All I ate was a
salad. I had a salad and I paid $195.
And I went back and he said, "Okay, now
you see now that's a dinner." He said,
"You probably had what? A nice bottle of
wine. You had a steak." I said, "No,
actually I ate a fetush salad. It was
$195."
And he's he says, "How
[laughter] how could that possibly be?"
I said, "You told me stop trying to save
the government money."
>> So I wanted a foo. Everything was one
price.
>> I ate the fouch. [laughter]
But you can't win in government. You
just can't win. Especially when you're
in an organization like the CIA where
nobody cares about the money,
>> right?
>> The money is the last thing that you
should worry about.
>> They just throw it at the wall, see
whatever sticks. That's what it is.
Crazy. I do.
>> I I went up to Excuse me one second. Uh
a couple of days after 911,
>> I went up to Kofheer Black, who was the
director of the CIA's counterterrorism
program. I said, 'Koffer, I've got an
idea for an operation that I want to
pass by you. He put up his hands like
this and he says,"Listen, whatever it
is, just do it. I have so much money, I
can't possibly spend it all."
>> Wow.
>> One of the things that the CIA did right
after 9/11, because we had so much
money, everybody went business class. No
matter where you were going, anywhere in
the world, business class, knock
yourselves out.
>> Absolutely not. And that's where your
money goes. Where most Americans are
working two jobs to survive.
>> That's right.
>> That's where your money goes. That's
your government corruption.
Unbelievable. All right. With that,
let's kind of transition to what is
Trump doing. So, he ran on the platform
that he would stop the war and he would
clean up the government this time and
all of that. All right. Opinions. I
mean, so far I feel like he's like not
even doing 20% of what he said he would
do.
>> I have to agree. I I deep down I want to
give Donald Trump the benefit of the
doubt.
>> Right.
>> Cuz you know the what's going on, you
know, he's like it's daunting.
>> It's daunting.
>> No president fully understands the power
of the deep state, right? And when you
only have eight years, and in this case,
Donald Trump has four years. You can't
defeat the deep state in four years. And
the first four years he was just sort of
learning the ropes and allowed himself
to be played by the deep state. When you
name the likes of Mike Pompeo who's like
the godfather of the deep state and then
replace him with Gina Haspel who's the
poster child for the deep state and you
have you have John Bolton as your
national security adviser you know who
is the guy to perpetuate the deep state.
Then you know what the heck are you
thinking? What do you think is going to
happen?
>> Right?
>> So he came the second time. He wants to
do the right thing. He uh points
bonafide outsiders to some of these
important positions,
but then he buckles to the neocons.
>> Absolutely.
>> Donald Trump said he was going to end
the the Russia Ukraine war in 24 hours.
Nobody actually believed he was going to
be able to do that. But we all I think
believe that he was going to put
sufficient pressure on the Ukra on the
Ukrainian government to force them to
come to some sort of an agreement with
the Russians. everybody.
>> He started well. He started um he
started right with Zalinski in the White
House and I mean they laid on him and
not only him but also um yeah absolutely
Jay De Vance and uh but then something
changed like he goes to Vatican as I as
I recall it was a funeral of of the pope
right
>> and he sits quietly with Zanski this
former you know actor that used to play
piano with his dick. It's real guys.
Yeah he did.
>> He did. Yeah. And um and things change.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't think it was Zalinski. Zalinski
could not convince anybody by himself.
Certainly not.
>> So obviously he's you know again being
manipulated by forces. It's almost like
people say like whoever talks the last
to Donald Trump. That's exactly what's
going to pass. That's that's
embarrassing.
>> Unfortunately, that's what I've heard
from insiders, too. He's he's easily
influenced by the last person he's
spoken to.
>> So I'm I'm curious. Um this is a good
segue into the Elon Trump and after
>> Elon Musk and Trump um coordination
efforts. Your opinion on do you think
that the whole um split of Elon and
Trump was coordinated by them on
purpose?
>> I don't think so.
>> I I don't think so either. Um I don't
think Elon Musk would have tweeted what
he tweeted about Donald Trump being
implicated in the Epstein fire. But now
the left wants the Epstein files out.
>> Yeah.
>> So
>> yeah,
>> the thing is [clears throat] I think
Okay, I I'll tell you what I think and
then I'm interested what John thinks
about this. So I think that Elon is a
genius, but I also think that he's a
baby.
>> I think he's very reactive baby.
>> And you know, maybe it's his asberers.
Maybe it's his like, hey, there's
nothing wrong with that, right? I'm very
emotional myself and I don't tolerate
when, you know, people throw [__] at me.
So, I understand Elon's position. I
always said from the get-go, hey, guy
came in, you called him. He didn't just
insert himself in the government. You
called him. So, guy comes in, takes care
of Dodge, cuts whatever needs to be cut.
I mean, obviously like sending what was
it? Condoms. Uh, remind me again where
where were they sending condoms?
>> It was like to Africa, some place.
>> Yeah. Some African place. And uh people,
by the way, it was a misconception. and
they said Gaza, but not the Gaza that
that we know. It was an African uh place
somewhere. So obviously he knew that
there there's a lot of crap that's go
that goes on and we need to kind of get
rid of it and he did. But then his
company kind of, you know, nosedived
because of what he was doing. So he
sacrificed years of building Tesla,
which he acquired when Tesla was dying,
his in his own words. So here's the
dying company that he saved with blood
and sweat and investments and all of a
sudden he went in to do greater good in
Washington and his companies took a huge
hit. Not just Tesla but also other
companies. Uh people were literally
burning cars down. So a little
appreciation you know would have been
nice.
>> Well let let me disagree.
>> Okay.
>> Elon Musk knew nothing about how
government operates.
He you can't you can't just go in and
fire people. We have this thing called
the Civil Service Act,
>> right?
>> And so he would go in and say, "We're
laying off 200 people." Uh, sorry,
chief. No, we're not. That's not how
Washington works. You have to work
within the confines of the law. And then
he would just move on to the next, you
know, to the Social Security
Administration or the Office of
Personnel Management or 14 people at the
CIA because they were working in DEI,
whatever.
>> Yeah. No, you can't do that. You can
transfer people around. You can make
their job so uncomfortable that they
leave on their own valition, but you
can't just go in and say, "I'm going to
down."
>> John, I I actually
>> But that's but that's real life. Yeah.
It takes time. We have three separate
but equal branches of government. If you
want to cut government,
>> you have to go to Congress and have them
authorize the cut.
>> I get your point completely. The problem
is I think that doing things old way and
giving them oh let's go to Congress
since when Congress made any right
decisions about anything. So the problem
is I'm I'm Tim here like get rid of
them.
>> That's the situation we have. It's not
that you can just decide I'm going to
I'm just going to cut Congress out
because they're ins they're inefficient.
>> It's that that's the law.
>> Yeah.
>> You have to abide by the law. You know,
everybody filed federal lawsuits against
Doge and against uh Elon Musk, and
they've all won.
>> Yeah.
>> Because you can't just bring this guy,
he's just some guy uh in and say, "Yeah,
you're fired and we're closing that
office and we're not going to do this
anymore." And you can't do that.
>> What I would agree with, it should have
been better coordinated. I agree with
that. But I think that uh the instincts
of Iran is right. government is full of
fat and they need to go and they are you
know you just talked about it like you
know it's it's full of fat it's full of
extra money they need to go but we need
a better system
>> what they should have done is to work
with Congress before the election
>> agreed so they had a plan
>> you know what was it the you know plan
to save America or whatever the heck it
was called in the '9s that Nuke Gingrich
had
>> um where they would come up with a plan
to say we're going to slash the federal
budget
And this is how we're going to do it. If
we win a majority in the two houses of
Congress, which they ended up winning,
and the White House, which they also
ended up winning, implement this plan.
Because remember, on budget issues,
there's there's no um filibuster,
>> right?
>> You only need 51 votes in the Senate or
50 plus the vice president.
>> Uh and in the House, it's just a simple
majority of, you know, 50% plus one,
>> right? Uh but they they didn't even like
it didn't even occur to them
>> that there's a there's a an
appropriations and authorization process
that you go through to do this kind of
thing. They just figured out we'll just
wing it. We'll just fire everybody. They
can sue us and we'll probably win. And
they didn't win. They lost.
>> Yeah. So I I would agree with that. They
should have had a better better plan. Uh
let's go back to Elon Musk and Donald
Trump. I mean this fight was like a
children like the children.
>> Yeah. But Donald Trump addressed it as
an adult. I agree. He had a good
comments. He said, "I don't know what's
wrong with that." And he didn't.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, he's the president after all, and
you know, he's smart enough to know how
to address these situations. As I
recall, he said, "You know, I helped
Elan a lot." So, he was kind of hurt.
You could tell he was hurt.
>> Yeah, he was.
>> Um, and then Elan apologized, which was
a little bit too late, but still,
>> what's the deal with this Epstein files?
>> What? Who are they protecting and why
haven't they come out yet?
>> And why why would Dylan get so dirty to
put
>> he knew a buzzword to throw out into
social media? I think to get people
>> Yeah. Yeah. And it was like what what
was the retweet count? It was like
incredible amount.
>> Yeah.
>> So why do you think that happened?
>> I think that Elon Musk was angry and
hurt and lashing out.
>> Yeah.
>> Also keep in mind Elon Musk didn't have
access to the Epstein files.
>> Yes. So, how would he know if Donald
Trump is in the Epstein fuzz or not? I
think Donald Trump probably is not other
than the fact that he had been to the
island once or twice.
>> Yeah. He's also was pretty, as I
understand, he had good relationship
with Epstein himself.
>> Everybody did.
>> The Clintons did. He did. Bush did.
Everybody Everybody did. Kenned.
>> Obama's sure. Everybody did.
>> Let's get real, guys. I don't fold these
people, okay? So, people, oh my gosh,
you're on Epste. I could have been on a
island. Excuse me. Because it was an
operation. This is what people don't
understand. John could have been there.
You could have been there. So let's say
some guy who you don't really know who
he is other than he's a financeier.
That's how he presented himself and
that's how people talked about he's a
financeier. Some financier invites you
on a private jet on an island. Yeah. You
wouldn't go. Like how the heck do you
know what you're walking into? This
happened to I come from a Hollywood
background. This happened to me all the
time. Oh, there's a party. Guess what?
You network during the party. So, for
us, it was like a every actor will tell
you, every starter, producer, director
will tell you be at every freaking party
because that's where networking happens,
right? So, these people are like, "Okay,
well, you know, Prince is going to be
there." What? Prince Andrew? Like,
wouldn't you go? You wouldn't go. Of
course you would go. Of course you
would. Everything is funded, right?
>> The situation with Bobby Kennedy, uh,
Jr., I think, is is very telling. Yes.
>> For a while people were saying, "Oh my
god, Bobby Kennedy Jr. was on Epstein's
plane." And he said, "Yeah, I was with
my wife and all my kids."
>> Right?
>> Because
>> he said his wife had met Epstein at some
dinner party, whatever in New York and
mentioned that they were going to Palm
Beach for Easter.
>> And he said, "Oh, do you want a ride? I
have to stop in Palm Beach and I'm gonna
go to my island from from there.
>> There you go.
>> And she said, "Sure, we'd love a ride."
And so the Kennedy family got on the
plane in New York. They flew to Palm
Beach. They got off and Epstein went on
to the island. That was it. And for a
little while, people tried to make a big
deal that oh my god, Bobby Kennedy was
on the Epstein plane.
>> Do you think that's kind of like the
same case as Trump?
>> I do.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah,
>> I do.
>> I agree with that. And like I said, I
But the list itself doesn't bother me.
It could be anybody in there. What
bothers me is who actually like Prince
Andrew for example found out I mean
you're not stupid like let's say we take
your example you go on an island
everything was set up for you it's great
okay we're having fun and all of a
sudden a very young girl walks in okay
where you're stupid you're not going to
ask an age you're just going to like oh
go and her excuse is my language no like
this is this is the problem I have so
which from all of these people in the
list which one of them actually had
sexual relationship on
>> there was cameras everywhere, right?
Like we know who was implicated and
who's not,
>> right?
>> Yeah. So that's the question I have.
Like those bothered me, right? He could
have been I mean, God's sakes, Stephen
Hawkins was there. Yeah. But what
>> he's not he's not banging a
six-year-old.
>> Exactly. So I mean this is why I don't
care about the list. What I care about
is what Dim Benino and what's his name?
Kesh Patal are doing with the tapes. And
why why is it so freaking secret? Wasn't
cash batal all about oh it's with the
FBI FBI so corrupt well now you are
leading FBI so what now
>> that's exactly right
>> why do you think these two who I
actually liked I really enjoyed you know
kesh Patal his interviews I was like
okay this guy can go in and clean up
corruption in the FB maybe I'm naive to
think so but and then of course they you
know get demand another one who's
trusted by everybody including media and
both of them come out and like like two
little guilty kids.
>> They have a right to their opinion. But
as someone who has worked as a public
defender, as a prosecutor, who's been in
that prison system, who's been in the
Metropolitan Detention Center, who's
been in segregated housing, um you know,
a suicide when you see one. And that's
what that was.
>> He killed himself.
>> He just killed himself. Like I I've I've
seen evidence and they get so panicky
about I've seen it. Like,
>> okay, dude.
>> They don't want you to see it.
>> No, no, no. But they've seen it.
>> I actually believe that he killed
himself and I've said it from the very
beginning only because I've been in
prison
>> and I know that everybody in the prison
industrial complex
>> has his head up his ass.
>> Okay,
>> listen. To be a prison guard, you only
need two qualifications. You either have
to have or be working on a GED and no
felony convictions. I can't tell you how
many times prisoners had to do mail call
because the guard who was supposed to do
mail call
>> couldn't read. That's who we have
guarding our prisons.
>> Even the ones that he was in. I mean,
this is a
>> especially especially the ones that he
the the one that he was in because
nobody wants to be in the violent
prisons. If you have two ounces of
brains, you're going to be in the
minimum security or the low security,
not the maximum security MDC,
Metropolitan Detention Center.
>> And so I remember speaking to a friend
of mine who was convinced that he was
murdered. And I said, "Look at this one
step at a time. The guards are not
supposed to work more than eight hours."
Okay?
>> Both of the guards on that unit had
worked double shifts, 16 hours,
>> right? Because they're short staffed.
You're not supposed to work more than
eight hours. Okay, they do it anyway.
Number one. Number two, the camera was
broken. Guess what? All the cameras are
broken.
>> That's why people are always having sex
in the chapel or underneath the stairs
when you go down to the mail room or in
the gym.
>> How do you know that?
>> Because I'm like, that's what people do
and you can't control yourselves for six
months that you're here. [laughter]
>> Stop. [snorts]
Okay. you know, so [laughter]
so the cameras are always broken.
>> If somebody is suicidal or thought to be
suicidal, he's supposed to be placed in
a room with windows on four sides. And
you have volunteer prisoners just
sitting there in a chair like this,
staring at him 4-hour shifts, 24 hours a
day to make sure that he doesn't kill
himself. And he's not given sheets. His
sheets are made of paper so he can't tie
a knot and hang himself. And every step
of the way there was a breakdown.
>> Okay. The question I have, do you think
that's intentional breakdown? Cuz
though,
>> that's a different question.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Probably.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. So, you think that Okay. Now,
let's talk about his mindset. Abstin.
This is a guy who I mean, obviously, he
knows what he got himself into. He's not
stupid. He he was in jail before, as I
understand, and they, you know, freed
him. So, he's dealing with some serious
uh people out there, some very heavy
weights. So, he he killed let's say he
wanted to kill himself.
>> Um it's obviously not because he's, you
know, sad about what he did. It's
obviously because he knows that he's in
the walking information hazard.
>> So, why do you think do first of all, do
you think a psychopath like him or
sociopath like him, you got to be, uh
would even attempt that like
>> Oh, yeah. And I think especially for a
sociopath, it would be a a rather um
easy decision
>> really.
>> Yeah. It would be devoid of emotion.
He would consider just the
practicalities. He was what 60 years old
almost 60 years old.
>> He's looking at probably second offense
probably 25 27 years.
>> Uh and pedophile pedophiles are not
eligible to go to um to minimum security
work camps. He's gonna be in prison for
the rest of his days,
>> right?
>> And so it's better to be dead.
>> Interesting. Well, yeah. I mean, I don't
know unless I look at certain, you know,
videos or evidence and so far they
produced absolutely nothing. That's the
question mark for me. Okay. He killed
himself. Great. Show us.
>> Show us what you have. What's the deal?
>> Yeah. What's the What's the big secret?
Just lay out the evidence.
>> Exactly. And everyone lay out the
evidence and everybody's going to walk
away. Right. Yeah. Yeah,
>> but they won't
>> they won't lay out the evidence.
[music]